<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>A fairy worked in a freezer: Temperature Penalty by Race</name>
	<author>jptrrs</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>JPT.TemperatureByRace</packageId>
	<modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
      <displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
   </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>
  "Nanami, I recall you're a magical ice fairy who can only survive when it's below freezing?"
  "Indeed."
  "And Daniel, you're some flesh-mashine hybrid thing, right?"
  "Yes, I'm an android."
  "And you don't mind freezing temperatures that would quickly kill a human?"
  "I have my limits, but yeah."
  "So, say you two were to make us some nice leather hats while the room is a bit below freezing. The temperature wouldn't bother you, correct?"
  "Oh no no no. It's the workbench that's affected by temperature, not us!"
  
  In all fairness, since vanilla only has humans, it doesn't matter there. However, once you get modded races that can also -or perhaps only- survive in comparatively extreme temperatures, the fact that the workspeed penalty is based on fixed temperatures becomes annoying.
  This mod changes the x0.7 Bad Temperature modifier to consider the currently working pawns race, only applying it if they are outside of their base comfortable temperature (any effects from apparel ect. are ignored).
  Do note that while the message upon placing any workbench still shows, the actual penalty won't be there.
  Now you can have your ice faries, magma golems, robots and spacebugs work in endless blizzards or active volcanos without suffering a penalty! (*None of the former included)
  

  This mod was commissioned by me and written by jptrrs.
  </description>
  
	<url></url>
</ModMetaData>